(Leonard:)Starting Saturday morning,
"Star Wars" marathon.
- Woo-hoo.
- Movies or video games?
Or board games? Or trading-card games?
Or Legos? Or dress-up? Or comic books?
(Sheldon:)Or dramatic readings of novelizations?
(Sheldon:)Yes to all.
(Leonard:)We are going to play the online game.
(Sheldon:)The online game? Bully.
(Amy:)As much as I'm sure Sheldon would enjoy...
(Amy:)...playing intergalactic make-believe,
he and I have plans.
(Amy:)We are attending my Aunt Flora's
93rd birthday party.
(Sheldon:)Just tell her I can't come.
(Amy:)She'll be disappointed if we don't show.
(Sheldon:)She's 93.
She won't be disappointed for very long.
(Amy:)Hang on. I followed all the protocols...
(Amy:)...set forth by you
in the Relationship Agreement.
l made a written request
72 hours in advance.
Checked the tire pressure on the car.
l contacted the
Centers for Disease Control...
(Amy:)...to find out what shots they
recommend for travel to Orange County.
FYl, it's none.
(Sheldon:)Amy, the Relationship Agreement...
(Sheldon:)...was not designed
for either one of us to get our way.
(Amy:)You use it to get your way.
l use it to get the right way.
(Sheldon:)The fact that the right way
is also my way is a happy coincidence.
(Amy:)You gave me your word.
You're coming with me.
(Leonard:)We'll miss you, Sheldon.
Yeah? Well, who wants
to spend the whole weekend...
(Sheldon:)...running around a bunch of pretend
planets battling made-up monsters?
(Sheldon:)- That's for babies.
- Yeah, but it's got lightsabers.
Yeah. Please, Amy, it's got lightsabers.